[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "What is the very latest on this manhunt for this very dangerous man?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "very", "latest", "on", "this", "manhunt", "for", "this", "very", "dangerous", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Well, the sheriff's department just came out and spoke with reporters.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "sheriff", "'s", "department", "just", "came", "out", "and", "spoke", "with", "reporters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "Or do they fear the whole thing has been a trail he's laid down to put them off where he really is?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "they", "fear", "the", "whole", "thing", "has", "been", "a", "trail", "he", "'s", "laid", "down", "to", "put", "them", "off", "where", "he", "really", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "It's very difficult to tell.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "difficult", "to", "tell", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "What else can you tell me about the kind of firearms he may have?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "about", "the", "kind", "of", "firearms", "he", "may", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "The police have been vague.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "police", "have", "been", "vague", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Is it some anniversary of his time with the LAPD?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "some", "anniversary", "of", "his", "time", "with", "the", "LAPD", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Something very significant.", "answer_tokens": ["Something", "very", "significant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["LAPD"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RBR", "RB", ",", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Is that what the police think they're dealing with, somebody who just has been harboring resentment and is now settling scores?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "the", "police", "think", "they", "'re", "dealing", "with", ",", "somebody", "who", "just", "has", "been", "harboring", "resentment", "and", "is", "now", "settling", "scores", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "It's a little difficult to tell because the people we've spoken to are people who knew him in much happier times, that he was much more bubbly, much more normal.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "little", "difficult", "to", "tell", "because", "the", "people", "we", "'ve", "spoken", "to", "are", "people", "who", "knew", "him", "in", "much", "happier", "times", ",", "that", "he", "was", "much", "more", "bubbly", ",", "much", "more", "normal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "It's a pretty worrying situation, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "pretty", "worrying", "situation", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "It certainly is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "certainly", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "What is your overview of what is going on here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "overview", "of", "what", "is", "going", "on", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Well, the circumstances today were certainly extraordinarily tragic.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "circumstances", "today", "were", "certainly", "extraordinarily", "tragic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBG", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "When you hear the nature of that threat, what do you -- what do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "hear", "the", "nature", "of", "that", "threat", ",", "what", "do", "you", "--", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, certainly very chilling, and now that we know that he in fact is acting out on his concerns even more significant.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "certainly", "very", "chilling", ",", "and", "now", "that", "we", "know", "that", "he", "in", "fact", "is", "acting", "out", "on", "his", "concerns", "even", "more", "significant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Do you remember him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "First off, we don't know what the catalyst was.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "off", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "the", "catalyst", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "And you probably gave it to him when you met him when he was about to go off for military service, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "probably", "gave", "it", "to", "him", "when", "you", "met", "him", "when", "he", "was", "about", "to", "go", "off", "for", "military", "service", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "That's correct.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Any idea what that could be about or do you assume it has to do with the fact that you happen to be running the LAPD when he got -- he got laid off?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "idea", "what", "that", "could", "be", "about", "or", "do", "you", "assume", "it", "has", "to", "do", "with", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "happen", "to", "be", "running", "the", "LAPD", "when", "he", "got", "--", "he", "got", "laid", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Actually I only became aware of this other package about an hour and a half ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", "I", "only", "became", "aware", "of", "this", "other", "package", "about", "an", "hour", "and", "a", "half", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["LAPD"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "CC", ":", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "It's about 18 miles east of Los Angeles?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "about", "18", "miles", "east", "of", "Los", "Angeles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "That's correct, and it's very high mountains, very rugged mountains, and -- so if he's up in that area, incredibly difficult terrain to try and explore and search.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "correct", ",", "and", "it", "'s", "very", "high", "mountains", ",", "very", "rugged", "mountains", ",", "and", "--", "so", "if", "he", "'s", "up", "in", "that", "area", ",", "incredibly", "difficult", "terrain", "to", "try", "and", "explore", "and", "search", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "CD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "What is the best thing that people can do if they have any sighting of this guy?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "best", "thing", "that", "people", "can", "do", "if", "they", "have", "any", "sighting", "of", "this", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well, certainly I think as the police forces in the California area are encouraging citizens, one, if you see this individual, and he's a very distinctive looking individual, huge.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "certainly", "I", "think", "as", "the", "police", "forces", "in", "the", "California", "area", "are", "encouraging", "citizens", ",", "one", ",", "if", "you", "see", "this", "individual", ",", "and", "he", "'s", "a", "very", "distinctive", "looking", "individual", ",", "huge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["LAPD"]}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Have you had any dealings with him?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "any", "dealings", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "No, the captain, if I understand it, had retired prior to my time at the LAPD, it was in the period of 2002-2009, so I had no awareness or any exposure to him.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "the", "captain", ",", "if", "I", "understand", "it", ",", "had", "retired", "prior", "to", "my", "time", "at", "the", "LAPD", ",", "it", "was", "in", "the", "period", "of", "2002-2009", ",", "so", "I", "had", "no", "awareness", "or", "any", "exposure", "to", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "And from all you've seen, from this manifesto that this gunman has put out, this alleged gunman, what is your reading of his state of mind and his motivation?", "question_tokens": ["And", "from", "all", "you", "'ve", "seen", ",", "from", "this", "manifesto", "that", "this", "gunman", "has", "put", "out", ",", "this", "alleged", "gunman", ",", "what", "is", "your", "reading", "of", "his", "state", "of", "mind", "and", "his", "motivation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "There's a tremendous amount of evidence of somebody who is extremely confused in this 6,000-word manifesto.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "tremendous", "amount", "of", "evidence", "of", "somebody", "who", "is", "extremely", "confused", "in", "this", "6,000-word", "manifesto", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "What is going on here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "on", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Clearly, this is not about attention.", "answer_tokens": ["Clearly", ",", "this", "is", "not", "about", "attention", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Monica", "Monica"]}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Did you know her father?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "her", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Yes, I've known Monica and her family since Monica was about 11 or 12 years old.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'ve", "known", "Monica", "and", "her", "family", "since", "Monica", "was", "about", "11", "or", "12", "years", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Was that ever something she was concerned about?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "ever", "something", "she", "was", "concerned", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Is everybody in a state of terror about this?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "everybody", "in", "a", "state", "of", "terror", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Are you any nearer to knowing?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "any", "nearer", "to", "knowing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "I think we're 12 hours from the snow starting so we should know exactly at this point in time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "'re", "12", "hours", "from", "the", "snow", "starting", "so", "we", "should", "know", "exactly", "at", "this", "point", "in", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "What day would that fly be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "day", "would", "that", "fly", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "IN", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Tomorrow morning.", "answer_tokens": ["Tomorrow", "morning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Where do you think we are with this whole gun control debate right now?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "think", "we", "are", "with", "this", "whole", "gun", "control", "debate", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Hard to say because there are so many aspects to it and so many different positions.", "answer_tokens": ["Hard", "to", "say", "because", "there", "are", "so", "many", "aspects", "to", "it", "and", "so", "many", "different", "positions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "What is wrong with forcing through something which actually reduces the ability of the criminally minded and the mentally deranged from getting their hands on this gun that I'm currently being seen firing here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "wrong", "with", "forcing", "through", "something", "which", "actually", "reduces", "the", "ability", "of", "the", "criminally", "minded", "and", "the", "mentally", "deranged", "from", "getting", "their", "hands", "on", "this", "gun", "that", "I", "'m", "currently", "being", "seen", "firing", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "DT", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Absolutely no harm done if you do that, if you do it right.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "no", "harm", "done", "if", "you", "do", "that", ",", "if", "you", "do", "it", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick"]}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "First of all, what was your reaction to him being fired by Fox and being called the worst pundit of last year?", "question_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "to", "him", "being", "fired", "by", "Fox", "and", "being", "called", "the", "worst", "pundit", "of", "last", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Well, Dick is a friend of mine for 20 years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Dick", "is", "a", "friend", "of", "mine", "for", "20", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fox"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "You mean Hurricane Sandy?", "question_tokens": ["You", "mean", "Hurricane", "Sandy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Or is that really just a convenient excuse?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "that", "really", "just", "a", "convenient", "excuse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "No, it's somewhere in the middle.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "somewhere", "in", "the", "middle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marco Rubio"]}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "What was your reaction when you saw that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "saw", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "I'm a very, very big Marco Rubio fan.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "very", ",", "very", "big", "Marco", "Rubio", "fan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "I mean, at what stage does the drone activity cease to be legitimate targeting of terrorism and become a kind of glorified, very brutal, very lethal fishing expedition?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "at", "what", "stage", "does", "the", "drone", "activity", "cease", "to", "be", "legitimate", "targeting", "of", "terrorism", "and", "become", "a", "kind", "of", "glorified", ",", "very", "brutal", ",", "very", "lethal", "fishing", "expedition", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Well, it has to be done very carefully, very uniquely.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "has", "to", "be", "done", "very", "carefully", ",", "very", "uniquely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "And they'll be curious, what kind of emotions do you go through when you hear of this kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["And", "they", "'ll", "be", "curious", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "emotions", "do", "you", "go", "through", "when", "you", "hear", "of", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "I'll tell you, I share that mother's joy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "share", "that", "mother", "'s", "joy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "What kind of advice would you give his mother if you had the chance?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "advice", "would", "you", "give", "his", "mother", "if", "you", "had", "the", "chance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I would say surround yourself with family.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "surround", "yourself", "with", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Have you had the chance to talk to Jaycee about what happened with this little boy Ethan?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "the", "chance", "to", "talk", "to", "Jaycee", "about", "what", "happened", "with", "this", "little", "boy", "Ethan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Jaycee and I talk, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Jaycee", "and", "I", "talk", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jaycee", "Ethan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "How is her progress coming along?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "her", "progress", "coming", "along", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Active in the foundation, as we all are.", "answer_tokens": ["Active", "in", "the", "foundation", ",", "as", "we", "all", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "And her two little children, how are they doing?", "question_tokens": ["And", "her", "two", "little", "children", ",", "how", "are", "they", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Very well, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "well", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Are they able to lead a kind of normal life now?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "able", "to", "lead", "a", "kind", "of", "normal", "life", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "That's what the privacy is all about, is the ability for them to live as normal a life as possible.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "the", "privacy", "is", "all", "about", ",", "is", "the", "ability", "for", "them", "to", "live", "as", "normal", "a", "life", "as", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Does part of you wish he had, too, lost his life, when eventually the kidnapping was exposed?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "part", "of", "you", "wish", "he", "had", ",", "too", ",", "lost", "his", "life", ",", "when", "eventually", "the", "kidnapping", "was", "exposed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", ",", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "You know, I don't place a whole lot of thought on that.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "place", "a", "whole", "lot", "of", "thought", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]